<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-04-13T01:57:42.410Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-04-13T01:57:42.410Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Chief Legal Officer: The Problem With SEC's Howey Test Isn't Its Age]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/woZFLgib/coinbase-chief-legal-officer-the-problem-with-secs-howey-test-isnt-its-age</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/woZFLgib/coinbase-chief-legal-officer-the-problem-with-secs-howey-test-isnt-its-age"/>
        <updated>2023-04-10T16:25:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Chief Legal Officer Paul Grewal discussed the "Howey Test," which the SEC uses as its yard stick for whether a crypto asset should be regulated as a security, and told Decrypt's Stacy Elliott and Dan Roberts the issue with it isn't that it's old (the case is from 1946) but how it's being applied to modern technology. Watch and make sure to subscribe to the gm podcast on Apple or Spotify.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized Pictures Plots Its Next Web3 Grant for Filmmakers]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/WlVsgaOs/decentralized-pictures-plots-its-next-web3-grant-for-filmmakers</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/WlVsgaOs/decentralized-pictures-plots-its-next-web3-grant-for-filmmakers"/>
        <updated>2023-04-08T13:15:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Leo Matchett from Web3 film funding platform Decentralized Pictures tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson at Outer Edge LA about DCP's just announced iPhone Filmmaking Initiative, which will support aspiring filmmakers who create a short film on their iPhones, and will be determined via DCP's crypto-native on-chain voting system.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 YouTuber CryptoStache: Gaming Will Be the Catalyst That Takes NFTs Mainstream]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Exb7eWKj/web3-youtuber-cryptostache-gaming-will-be-the-catalyst-that-takes-nfts-mainstream</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/Exb7eWKj/web3-youtuber-cryptostache-gaming-will-be-the-catalyst-that-takes-nfts-mainstream"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T02:51:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web3 gaming YouTuber CryptoStache talks to Decrypt's Jason Nelson at Outer Edge LA about why Web3 gaming will bring NFTs mainstream, the partnerships that prove it's already happening, how gamers will change their tune on NFTs, and how the terminology is likely to change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fordefi Aims to Dramatically Simplify the Institutional Crypto Wallet]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/LGxyFJP5/fordefi-aims-to-dramatically-simplify-the-institutional-crypto-wallet</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/LGxyFJP5/fordefi-aims-to-dramatically-simplify-the-institutional-crypto-wallet"/>
        <updated>2023-04-07T02:39:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Steve H., VP of sales from Fordefi, which raised $18 million in funding last year, tells Decrypt's Jason Nelson at Outer Edge LA how Fordefi uses multi-party computation to make signing transactions on an institutional crypto wallet much simpler—no seed phrase needed.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gm: Canadian Bitcoin Miner Hut 8 Is Heading West]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5AGD2ifd/gm-canadian-bitcoin-miner-hut-8-is-heading-west</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/5AGD2ifd/gm-canadian-bitcoin-miner-hut-8-is-heading-west"/>
        <updated>2023-04-06T21:40:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Toronto-based Bitcoin mining company Hut 8 recently announced a merger with U.S. Bitcoin Corp that will take it into Texas, Nebraska, and New York. Hut 8 CEO Jaime Leverton joined Dan Roberts and Stacy Elliott to talk expanding into the U.S., dealing with regulatory pushback post-FTX, why Texas is such a hotspot, and where she'd like to expand globally down the road (the climates may surprise you). Watch and make sure to subscribe to the gm podcast on Apple or Spotify.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gm: Kevin Owocki Wants to Regenerate DeFi]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/knbMLd17/gm-kevin-owocki-wants-to-regenerate-defi</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/knbMLd17/gm-kevin-owocki-wants-to-regenerate-defi"/>
        <updated>2023-04-01T14:23:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Move over, DeFi—ReFi is coming? Gitcoin founder Kevin Owocki has stepped away from DeFi grant-giving machine Gitcoin as it fully decentralizes and is now focused on regenerative finance (huh?) and ReFi incubator Supermodular. He aims to "regenerate the regenerators." He explained it all to Dan Roberts and Liam Kelly, and also talks DAO structure, crypto factions, NFT use cases, his book "Greenpilled," and much more. Watch and make sure to subscribe to the gm podcast on Apple or Spotify.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Aurory's Head of Production Left Ubisoft for Web3]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PqJHF0N9/why-aurorys-head-of-production-left-ubisoft-for-web3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/PqJHF0N9/why-aurorys-head-of-production-left-ubisoft-for-web3"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T21:24:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Aurory executive producer and head of production Jonathan Campeau tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin at GDC about how the first-generation of Web3 games came out of DeFi and are now evolving.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['We Don't Really Do the Corporate Thing Very Well' Says Jason Brink on Gala Games Approach]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/EDzHoKrt/we-dont-really-do-the-corporate-thing-very-well-says-jason-brink-on-gala-games-approach</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/EDzHoKrt/we-dont-really-do-the-corporate-thing-very-well-says-jason-brink-on-gala-games-approach"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T21:14:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With roughly 50 video games in its pipeline, Gala Games is all-in on Web3. Gala's President of Blockchain Jason Brink told Decrypt's Kate Irwin at GDC about the studio's ethos and weighs in on the different approaches to Web3 gaming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gm: Coinbase's Top Lawyer Gets Real on SEC]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mB7DMx7l/gm-coinbases-top-lawyer-gets-real-on-sec</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mB7DMx7l/gm-coinbases-top-lawyer-gets-real-on-sec"/>
        <updated>2023-03-28T16:36:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Paul Grewal is the Chief Legal Officer at Coinbase and a former U.S. magistrate judge in Northern California. He gave Dan Roberts and Stacy Elliott his candid takes on Sam Bankman-Fried and FTX, the SEC's crackdown on staking, the sanctioning of Tornado Cash, and more alpha on how Coinbase is approaching the current unfriendly US regulatory environment. Watch and make sure to subscribe to the gm podcast on Apple or Spotify.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Founder of Rotten Tomatoes Says Web3 Entertainment Isn’t Nearly Entertaining Enough Yet]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/ri2LLifZ/the-founder-of-rotten-tomatoes-says-web3-entertainment-isnt-nearly-entertaining-enough-yet</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/ri2LLifZ/the-founder-of-rotten-tomatoes-says-web3-entertainment-isnt-nearly-entertaining-enough-yet"/>
        <updated>2023-03-25T02:44:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rotten Tomatoes founder Patrick Lee, who has led companies at the intersection of technology and entertainment from Web1 to Web3, spoke to Decrypt's Sander Lutz at Outer Edge LA about the current state of decentralized gaming, film and television.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gm: How Gnosis Has Endured and Evolved]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Kxfs2Dmd/gm-how-gnosis-has-endured-and-evolved</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/Kxfs2Dmd/gm-how-gnosis-has-endured-and-evolved"/>
        <updated>2023-03-24T20:58:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Gnosis first launched in 2015 as a decentralized prediction market built on Ethereum. Now it's a DAO, a multi-sig wallet, a staking chain, and a vibrant community with its own GNO governance token. Co-founder and COO Friederike Ernst talked to Dan Roberts and Stacy Elliott about the careful evolution of Gnosis, decentralization impostors, account abstraction, DeFi UX failures, why Ethereum is the "Manhattan of crypto," and much more. Watch and make sure to subscribe to the gm podcast on Apple or Spotify.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Justin Aversano's Inspiration for Tarot-Themed NFT Photo Series 'Smoke and Mirrors']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/dkWNFMPb/justin-aversanos-inspiration-for-tarot-themed-nft-photo-series-smoke-and-mirrors</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/dkWNFMPb/justin-aversanos-inspiration-for-tarot-themed-nft-photo-series-smoke-and-mirrors"/>
        <updated>2023-03-24T20:03:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Justin Aversano, best known for his high-selling "Twin Flames" NFT photo series, joined Decrypt’s Andrew Hayward ahead of the upcoming L.A. exhibition for his new Ethereum NFT project "Smoke and Mirrors." He shared the wild inspiration behind the tarot-themed collection, and why—despite his growing profile—he opted not to exhibit at a major brand-name gallery.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Midnight Society’s Rob Bowling Talks Deadrop Launch and Working With Dr. Disrespect]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/yIc3fKH2/midnight-societys-rob-bowling-talks-deadrop-launch-and-working-with-dr-disrespect</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/yIc3fKH2/midnight-societys-rob-bowling-talks-deadrop-launch-and-working-with-dr-disrespect"/>
        <updated>2023-03-23T21:28:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Former "Call of Duty" developer Rob Bowling, now head of Midnight Society Studio, checked in with Decrypt's Kate Irwin at GDC and shared some behind-the-scenes statistics on how players are enjoying "Deadrop." The game saw 90,000 player hours over the weekend, with 97 minutes average play time per player, and their community size tripled in just a few days.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Big Brands Get Serious About NFTs: Salesforce, VW, Panerai, Absolute Labs at NFT Paris]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/BHN8nxxH/big-brands-get-serious-about-nfts-salesforce-vw-panerai-absolute-labs-at-nft-paris</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/BHN8nxxH/big-brands-get-serious-about-nfts-salesforce-vw-panerai-absolute-labs-at-nft-paris"/>
        <updated>2023-03-16T14:57:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On this panel from NFT Paris 2023 moderated by Decrypt's Dan Roberts, Web3 leads from some of the largest consumer and tech brands discuss their NFT strategies. Marc Mathieu of Salesforce, Tim Walther of VW Group, Eva Assayag of Panerai, and Samir Addamine of Absolute Labs joined the panel.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFT Entertainment Revolution: Warner Bros, Orange Comet, CyberBrokers and NFT Now at NFT Paris]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/ZWr09Uou/nft-entertainment-revolution-warner-bros-orange-comet-cyberbrokers-and-nft-now-at-nft-paris</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/ZWr09Uou/nft-entertainment-revolution-warner-bros-orange-comet-cyberbrokers-and-nft-now-at-nft-paris"/>
        <updated>2023-03-16T14:49:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At NFT Paris 2023, Decrypt’s Stephen Graves moderated a discussion about NFTs and the entertainment industry with Warner Bros’ NFT head Josh Hackbarth, CyberBrokers founder Josie Bellini, NFT Now founder Matt Medved and Dave Broome, CEO of Orange Comet, which has produced NFTs for Anthony Hopkins and The Walking Dead.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Step Inside the Armory of the NFT Collective 'Knights Who Say Nah']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/V6NGpw3i/step-inside-the-armory-of-the-nft-collective-knights-who-say-nah</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/V6NGpw3i/step-inside-the-armory-of-the-nft-collective-knights-who-say-nah"/>
        <updated>2023-03-15T20:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Knights Who Say Nah co-founder and project lead Nick Richey chats with Decrypt's Jason Nelson inside the group's armory of artifacts, shows off a historic Japanese tanto sword, and discusses why the preservation of historical artifacts is the best use case for NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>