<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2023-03-07T16:11:43.798Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2023-03-07T16:11:43.798Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFT Collector Gmoney: 'Marketplaces Have Nothing to Trade Without Creators']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/64foAcZa/nft-collector-gmoney-marketplaces-have-nothing-to-trade-without-creators</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/64foAcZa/nft-collector-gmoney-marketplaces-have-nothing-to-trade-without-creators"/>
        <updated>2023-03-07T04:22:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pseudonymous NFT collector Gmoney talks to Decrypt's Dan Roberts at NFT Paris about his Web3 luxury brand 9dcc, big brands getting into NFTs, the debate over creator royalty fees, and what will come next to the space.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Head of Product for IEX's Dispatch: 'We See Tokens as the Social Graph of Web3']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/CzC5ezdp/head-of-product-for-iexs-dispatch-we-see-tokens-as-the-social-graph-of-web3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/CzC5ezdp/head-of-product-for-iexs-dispatch-we-see-tokens-as-the-social-graph-of-web3"/>
        <updated>2023-03-07T04:17:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dispatch is a new Web3 marketing, messaging, and ad tech tool from IEX, the exchange fighting high-frequency trading and made famous in the book "Flash Boys" by Michael Lewis. Dispatch head of product Sean Spector sat down with Decrypt's Liam Kelly at NFT Paris to talk about Dispatch's product vision and why Web2 companies are jumping into Web3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gm: Neal Stephenson Maps Out the Metaverse]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mUwbgeAN/gm-neal-stephenson-maps-out-the-metaverse</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/mUwbgeAN/gm-neal-stephenson-maps-out-the-metaverse"/>
        <updated>2023-03-06T18:23:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Neal Stephenson coined the term “metaverse” in his seminal 1992 sci-fi hit novel “Snow Crash.” Now he’s helming a metaverse blockchain company called Lamina1 and advocating for one free and open metaverse. He spoke to Dan Roberts and Stephen Graves at length about what he got right and wrong in “Snow Crash,” goggles and flat screens, Big Tech, NFTs and digital ownership, and more. Watch and make sure to subscribe to the gm podcast on Apple or Spotify.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fireblocks Is Laser-Focused on the Picks and Shovels: Web3 Products Lead at ETH Denver]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/LFjwkdDI/fireblocks-is-laser-focused-on-the-picks-and-shovels-web3-products-lead-at-eth-denver</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/LFjwkdDI/fireblocks-is-laser-focused-on-the-picks-and-shovels-web3-products-lead-at-eth-denver"/>
        <updated>2023-03-06T16:15:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Omer Amsel, head of Web3 products at crypto custody and settlement provider Fireblocks, told Decrypt's Jason Nelson at ETH Denver about why crypto market cycles are best for building, how Fireblocks is focused on providing "picks and shovels," and why the company still believes in the long-term promise of Web3.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CEO of Video Streaming Platform Beem: Decentralization Lets 'Creators Regain Their Autonomy']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/kJsmUCBO/ceo-of-video-streaming-platform-beem-decentralization-lets-creators-regain-their-autonomy</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/kJsmUCBO/ceo-of-video-streaming-platform-beem-decentralization-lets-creators-regain-their-autonomy"/>
        <updated>2023-03-06T14:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mihai Crasneanu, Co-founder and CEO of Beem, describes Beem as "a mix of YouTube, Twitch, Zoom, and Clubhouse" that runs as a decentralized platform. He talked to Decrypt's Stephen Graves at NFT Paris about how it all works and how the platform is growing.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Calladita' Director Says NFT Funding Model He Used Is Already Gone Because Web3 Moves So Fast]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/qxlh2QZG/calladita-director-says-nft-funding-model-he-used-is-already-gone-because-web3-moves-so-fast</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/qxlh2QZG/calladita-director-says-nft-funding-model-he-used-is-already-gone-because-web3-moves-so-fast"/>
        <updated>2023-03-06T04:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Miguel Faus funded his upcoming film "Calladita" via NFT sales and a prize grant from Decentralized Pictures and Steven Soderbergh. He told Decrypt's Stephen Graves at NFT Paris about how the film process is progressing and how Web3 moves so quickly that the NFT funding model he used is already a thing of the past and other filmmakers need to find other ways to keep pushing the envelope.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase Protocols Lead Talks Plans for Base and NFT Marketplace]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/if8d95AZ/coinbase-protocols-lead-talks-plans-for-base-and-nft-marketplace</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/if8d95AZ/coinbase-protocols-lead-talks-plans-for-base-and-nft-marketplace"/>
        <updated>2023-03-05T01:27:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Coinbase protocols lead Jesse Pollak sat down with Decrypt's Jason Nelson at ETH Denver 2023 to talk about the company's innovation strategy and its plans to keep "iterating quickly" on products like Coinbase NFT and its newly announced Layer-2 blockchain Base and its efforts to become an "on-chain-native company."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['We Don't Want to Make Music NFTs Mainstream': DJ Agoria]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/phFrWZQN/we-dont-want-to-make-music-nfts-mainstream-dj-agoria</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/phFrWZQN/we-dont-want-to-make-music-nfts-mainstream-dj-agoria"/>
        <updated>2023-03-03T12:47:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[French electronic music producer DJ Agoria told Decrypt's Dan Roberts what excites him most about music NFTs, how it informs his work as a generative artist, and why Web3 is all about artists exploring "new ideas that were not possible in Web2."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Adidas Jumped Into Web3 and What It Plans Next]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/SYwSEgit/how-adidas-jumped-into-web3-and-what-it-plans-next</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/SYwSEgit/how-adidas-jumped-into-web3-and-what-it-plans-next"/>
        <updated>2023-03-02T12:21:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Adidas Web3 lead Erika Wykes-Sneyd told Decrypt's Dan Roberts the story of what prompted Adidas to get into crypto (it involves Elon Musk), what the brand has done so far with NFTs tied to physical apparel, and what it's considering next—including token-gated sneaker drops.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why 160-Year-Old Luxury Watch Maker Panerai Is Getting into NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/8DZX3S8s/why-160-year-old-luxury-watch-maker-panerai-is-getting-into-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/8DZX3S8s/why-160-year-old-luxury-watch-maker-panerai-is-getting-into-nfts"/>
        <updated>2023-03-02T03:50:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eva Assayag, Web3 lead at Panerai, sat down with Decrypt's Dan Roberts at NFT Paris to talk about Panerai's Web3 strategy, which will soon include a "digital passport" sold with every watch.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NFT Factory President: 'NFTs Will Be Active in a Bull or Bear Market']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/SG0hvMZz/nft-factory-president-nfts-will-be-active-in-a-bull-or-bear-market</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/SG0hvMZz/nft-factory-president-nfts-will-be-active-in-a-bull-or-bear-market"/>
        <updated>2023-03-02T03:37:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Karp, president of NFT Factory Paris and the founder of Non-Fungible Conference Lisbon, spoke to Decrypt's Dan Roberts at NFT Paris about the exploding Web3 community in Paris, the concept behind creating a physical gallery for NFTs, and how the existing art community understands NFTs because "everybody understands art."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What Attracted Artist Tom Sachs to NFTs? Community and Identity]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/bn9XyTHR/what-attracted-artist-tom-sachs-to-nfts-community-and-identity</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/bn9XyTHR/what-attracted-artist-tom-sachs-to-nfts-community-and-identity"/>
        <updated>2023-03-02T03:00:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tom Sachs is a conceptual artist whose work has been displayed in museums and galleries all over the world, but he told Decrypt's Dan Roberts at NFT Paris he never before felt part of an art movement—until he got into NFTs and Web3. He talked about Rocket Factory and the pull of Web3 art communities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arianee CEO: Big Consumer Brands Are Going to Take Web3 to 1 Billion Users]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/jsVfj33B/arianee-ceo-big-consumer-brands-are-going-to-take-web3-to-1-billion-users</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/jsVfj33B/arianee-ceo-big-consumer-brands-are-going-to-take-web3-to-1-billion-users"/>
        <updated>2023-03-02T02:38:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pierre-Nicolas Hurstel, CEO of Arianee, which offers enterprise software to consumer brands to help them launch NFTs tied to physical goods, spoke to Decrypt's Dan Roberts at NFT Paris about how much the NFT space is growing despite the bear market, how big consumer brands will take crypto mainstream, and how loyalty programs are going to be the next huge use case for NFTs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Salesforce Web3 Lead: Every Brand's Web Site Will Support Crypto Wallets]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/4T5Igqys/salesforce-web3-lead-every-brands-web-site-will-support-crypto-wallets</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/4T5Igqys/salesforce-web3-lead-every-brands-web-site-will-support-crypto-wallets"/>
        <updated>2023-03-02T02:08:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Salesforce's Web3 lead Marc Mathieu sat down with Decrypt's Dan Roberts at NFT Paris to talk about the CRM giant's crypto strategy, why "we had to" embrace Web3, and why the crypto wallet is "the new cookie" online.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Doodles CEO: Why In-Person Meetups Are Crucial for NFT Communities]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/httid2sc/doodles-ceo-why-in-person-meetups-are-crucial-for-nft-communities</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/httid2sc/doodles-ceo-why-in-person-meetups-are-crucial-for-nft-communities"/>
        <updated>2023-03-01T22:06:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Doodles CEO Julian Holguin, former president of Billboard, sat down with Decrypt's Stephen Graves at NFT Paris to talk about the strong vibes at the event and the importance of IRL meetups in Web3, what's next for Doodles and the community, and his prediction that many newer projects won't survive the crypto winter.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SuperRare Co-Founder: We Remain Committed to NFT Artist Royalties]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/nUWqIrqK/superrare-co-founder-we-remain-committed-to-nft-artist-royalties</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/nUWqIrqK/superrare-co-founder-we-remain-committed-to-nft-artist-royalties"/>
        <updated>2023-03-01T21:40:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SuperRare co-founder Jon Perkins sat down with Decrypt's Dan Roberts at NFT Paris to talk about the debate over artist royalties, SuperRare's roots in catering to artists, and building through a bear market.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gm: Meet the Brain Behind Avalanche]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rBypEFY1/gm-meet-the-brain-behind-avalanche</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/rBypEFY1/gm-meet-the-brain-behind-avalanche"/>
        <updated>2023-03-01T14:58:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Avalanche founder and Ava Labs CEO Emin Gun Sirer has been working on proof-of-work cryptocurrencies since before Bitcoin (seriously). He talked to Dan Roberts and Stacy Elliott about how Avalanche avoided FTX and how much damage SBF has done to crypto’s image with VCs, why institutions still aren’t backing away from crypto, why Avalanche will succeed in the long run, and trying to cater to both Wall Street institutions and DeFi degens. Watch and make sure to subscribe to the gm podcast on Apple or Spotify.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Founder of The Sandbox: 'Essential' to Metaverse That Users Own Their Digital Content]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/qjLwAXlw/founder-of-the-sandbox-essential-to-metaverse-that-users-own-their-digital-content</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/qjLwAXlw/founder-of-the-sandbox-essential-to-metaverse-that-users-own-their-digital-content"/>
        <updated>2023-03-01T04:09:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sebastien Borget, founder and COO of the metaverse realm The Sandbox, sat down wit Decrypt's Stephen Graves at NFT Paris to talk about the future of the open metaverse and true digital ownership, what's next for The Sandbox, and its current user numbers and stats.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Playboy's Next Step in Web3: MetaMansion in The Sandbox]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/rSoNJ53M/playboys-next-step-in-web3-metamansion-in-the-sandbox</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/rSoNJ53M/playboys-next-step-in-web3-metamansion-in-the-sandbox"/>
        <updated>2023-03-01T04:05:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Playboy's Web3 lead Liz Suman sat down with Decrypt's Dan Roberts at NFT Paris to tell the story of how the 70-year-old magazine brand got into Web3 and preview its upcoming MetaMansion in The Sandbox, which will give special access privileges to those with a Playboy Rabbitar NFT.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Orange Comet CEO: 'We're Trying to Build the Disney of Web3']]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/o75uDsuS/orange-comet-ceo-were-trying-to-build-the-disney-of-web3</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/o75uDsuS/orange-comet-ceo-were-trying-to-build-the-disney-of-web3"/>
        <updated>2023-02-28T22:37:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dave Broome, CEO of NFT design and production studio Orange Comet, spoke to Decrypt's Stephen Graves at NFT Paris about how his company takes "large, popular IP" and turns it into NFT content and Web3 worlds around it.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>