<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>urn:2022-08-31T17:16:03.640Z</id>
    <title>web3::cave</title>
    <updated>2022-08-31T17:16:03.640Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="index.html"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Silk Road to Buying ETH: How Musician Tycho Went Crypto]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/W2LG3C6J/from-silk-road-to-buying-eth-how-musician-tycho-went-crypto</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/W2LG3C6J/from-silk-road-to-buying-eth-how-musician-tycho-went-crypto"/>
        <updated>2022-08-27T19:56:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Scott Hansen aka Tycho, the musician, producer, and songwriter, tells Decrypt's Kate Irwin how he caught the crypto bug and why he believes Web3 can change the music industry for the better.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gm: Decentralized Pictures CEO on How Web3 Can Change Hollywood]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/YM2xNjS0/gm-decentralized-pictures-ceo-on-how-web3-can-change-hollywood</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/YM2xNjS0/gm-decentralized-pictures-ceo-on-how-web3-can-change-hollywood"/>
        <updated>2022-08-24T16:44:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decentralized Pictures, the nonprofit co-founded by Roman Coppola, is enabling on-chain voting to greenlight and fund film projects. CEO Leo Matchett tells Dan Roberts and Stephen Graves how the anti-crypto stigma in Hollywood is fading, how Web3 can bring more diversity to the film world and disrupt the traditional gatekeepers, and how he first got into crypto when he and Coppola set up a Bitcoin miner in an empty sound stage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt Learn: What Is a Node?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/ZGPeOz1o/decrypt-learn-what-is-a-node</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/explainers/ZGPeOz1o/decrypt-learn-what-is-a-node"/>
        <updated>2022-08-23T08:02:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this video, we’ll learn about a core component that defines Web3: blockchain nodes. A node is one of the many computers that power a decentralized network like Ethereum. Learn about the different types of nodes and why they’re part of the core infrastructure that make Web3 possible. Visit Infura.io today to start building. Written by: Clarissa Watson, Senior Tech Writer at ConsenSys.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt on the Street: An NFT Trip to Tiffany's, a Search for Status]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/tZvhuEpY/decrypt-on-the-street-an-nft-trip-to-tiffanys-a-search-for-status</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/tZvhuEpY/decrypt-on-the-street-an-nft-trip-to-tiffanys-a-search-for-status"/>
        <updated>2022-08-15T23:30:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In this episode of Decrypt on the Street, reporter Sander Lutz jumps through hoops in the hopes of obtaining an exclusive "NFTiff" from Tiffany & Co. Sander learns manners and spiritual awareness from two coaches, only to fall short of the digital brass ring.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[gm: Sam Bankman-Fried, Crypto Savior?]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/AXhGKs8E/gm-sam-bankman-fried-crypto-savior</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/AXhGKs8E/gm-sam-bankman-fried-crypto-savior"/>
        <updated>2022-08-12T16:45:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[FTX CEO Sam Bankman-Fried is the man of the moment in crypto as he has bailed out multiple insolvent companies. Some are calling him Atlas, some sarcastically calling him savior. Sam answers tough questions from Dan Roberts and Stacy Elliott on FTX's bailout strategy, the controversial Voyager loan, his market outlook, marketing mistakes by crypto lenders, FTX competitors Binance and Coinbase, his political donations, and what he's learned about management.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Musician and NFT Artist Jimmy Edgar Remains Skeptical on Music NFTs]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/SAjocwV9/why-musician-and-nft-artist-jimmy-edgar-remains-skeptical-on-music-nfts</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/SAjocwV9/why-musician-and-nft-artist-jimmy-edgar-remains-skeptical-on-music-nfts"/>
        <updated>2022-08-03T20:15:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Musician and NFT artist Jimmy Edgar is fully sold on NFT art, but not convinced yet on the uses of NFTs in the music world, he told Decrypt's Kate Irwin.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Avalanche's John Wu Talks Institutional Interest and Use Cases]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/XHPt24ug/avalanches-john-wu-talks-institutional-interest-and-use-cases</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/live-events/XHPt24ug/avalanches-john-wu-talks-institutional-interest-and-use-cases"/>
        <updated>2022-08-03T18:16:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ava Labs President John Wu sits for an extensive chat about institutional interest in crypto and DeFi (it has "absolutely not waned") and use cases of Avalanche with Decrypt's Dan Roberts at Avalanche House in Brooklyn on July 15, 2022.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt on the Street: Chipotle Says ‘Buy the Dip!’]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/UuV8fd5O/decrypt-on-the-street-chipotle-says-buy-the-dip</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/UuV8fd5O/decrypt-on-the-street-chipotle-says-buy-the-dip"/>
        <updated>2022-08-02T16:38:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In our latest Decrypt on the Street segment, reporter Sander Lutz investigates Chipotle’s recent crypto marketing campaign and talks to Chipotle customers about their sadness amid the crypto crash. 

Sander himself entered the contest hoping to get rich; instead he got a single cup of queso dip.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Civic Is Battling Web3 Bots and Spam: CPO JP Bedoya]]></title>
        <id>https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qRCnQ5Mi/how-civic-is-battling-web3-bots-and-spam-cpo-jp-bedoya</id>
        <link href="https://decrypt.co/videos/interviews/qRCnQ5Mi/how-civic-is-battling-web3-bots-and-spam-cpo-jp-bedoya"/>
        <updated>2022-08-02T15:25:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Decrypt's Jason Nelson reports from NFT Expoverse in LA with JP Bedoya, Chief Product Officer at Civic, the Web3 identity verification problem rolling out a new set of tools to keep people from spamming NFT drops to take advantage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>Decrypt</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>